I have not received any messages from EU
walk with the dogs
is on
that's what makes you count on only 1 income for one guy
here come theses bro
it doesn't work out if you keep counting on an egg in the chicken's ass
now screwed it up brother
fuel
finishing
find 1 post there
and favor
can pay at pix
i'm a sour family
I can't keep bothering you guy
other connections not
happen for me to be able to walk with dog
my idea is to go back to the stores
in the optics and try to do that pickup trap
you know pay daily and that's what I'm going to do bro
I'm low on money
red alert right
bro we go on this march
will give good
how are you
good Amanda is there
iron veil
I got here
no cheating wave
is on
now dude
I didn't get any pickup traps
it's on hand
I learned of a little place that
is a real old man to eat
and i'll get there fast
because their dinner time is different
it's early it's on
had gidelim
I will now create 1 account on Instagram
for people
really see that i have
dog walking experience
who knows how to attract more confidence
and feed this Instagram to be able to attract people
I'm interested in leaving your dog
for me to go around
is on
and then uncle
I have
EU follow
you are famous because you work with sales right
I'm Mc
Mc 2 underline s t
r is n k
God bless was worth
it's on the march there
we are together cousin is us
and now to sleep
it's hot
look at my skin here O poisonous O
then you open the glass
enter the light
it gets blurry that's it